[
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of India?",
    "answer": " New Delhi "
  },
  {
    "question": "Who wrote 'Srimad Bhagavad Gita'?",
    "answer": " Maharishi Veda Vyasa "
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the First President of India ?",
    "answer": " Dr. Rajendra Prasad "
  },
  {
    "question": "Python is a high-level __________ language known for its simplicity and readability.",
    "answer": "programming"
  },
  {
    "question": "HTML stands for Hypertext Markup __________.",
    "answer": "Language"
  },
  {
    "question": "In programming, a __________ is a named sequence of statements that performs a computation.",
    "answer": "function"
  },
  {
    "question": "CSS is used for __________ the appearance of web pages.",
    "answer": "styling"
  },
  {
    "question": "JavaScript is a __________-side scripting language used to add interactivity to web pages.",
    "answer": "client"
  },
  {
    "question": "SQL stands for Structured Query __________.",
    "answer": "Language"
  },
  {
    "question": "In object-oriented programming, a __________ is a blueprint for creating objects.",
    "answer": "class"
  },
  {
    "question": "Git is a popular __________ version control system used for tracking changes in source code.",
    "answer": "distributed"
  }
]